Lewis Carroll's Classic Fantasy Tale.
Alice Through the Looking Glass is a family, fantasy, tv
movie film directed by John Henderson.
A modern adaptation of the classic children's story 'Alice through the Looking
Glass', which continued on from the popular 'Alice in Wonderland' story.
This time Alice is played by the mother, who falls asleep while
reading the the bedtime story to her daughter.
Walking through the Looking Glass, Alice finds herself
in Chessland, a magical and fun world.
There she meets the Red and White Queens, as well as many other amusing friends on her
journey across the chessboard countryside onto become a crowned queen.
Alice, played by Kate Beckinsale.
White King, played by Geoffrey Palmer.
White Knight, played by Ian Holm.
Gnat, played by Steve Coogan.
White Queen, played by Penelope Wilton.
Little Alice, played by Charlotte Curley.
Alice through the Looking Glass is a 1998 British fantasy television film, based on Lewis
Carroll's 1871 book Through the Looking-Glass, and starring Kate Beckinsale.
The film was released on DVD in 2005.
The film explores themes of chess, based on novel or book,
queen, beautiful woman, alternate dimension.
The tone is lighthearted.